My friends and welcome to exercise number 51, we are asked to write a function to get the data value
stored in the node at given index recursively.
We have solved this exercise an interactive way in the previous video and exercise number 50.
So we are asked the same exercise both here and using recursion.
OK, so these are the methods that we have created in the previous exercises, and you can get the source
code from the resources folder.
Please read us five stars on Udemy to support us making new videos.
So I need to transform this method called get MS from iterative to recursion.
How to do it via both the video and think about it, I am waiting your your solutions.
And so that's begin and public and gapped and recursively Kerr certainly again, not it's specifying
the Hab and we are searching for the end position.
OK, thanks.
Head pointer off link at last and and the end as argument in end, as argument and returning the data
at index and OK.
So and count equal to zero.
If I had if I had equal equal to null, then edge case.
If that is equal to null, then return minus one.
OK.
This is their base case.
I told you in the recursion, there is a base case and a breaking case base case.
OK.
Again, please go back to the recursion section in order to understand that how recursion works.
OK, so if count equal to
and return the date, OK, this is the condition.
Also, if count equal equal to MN that you are going to search for, that third had the date.
Now recursively decrees MN and increase Hadoop next point.
So we need to go to move and call, get and recursively by passing.
The next had had the K'NEX and by decreasing and minus one because we are moving and one by one, one
by one, according to.
OK.
So let's go and test this method.
Let's go here.
Exercise number 51
Get that and not data value at a recursive
SO system.
I will copy it.
Like this.
And based its system that's stored at not in three linked list that get and recursively and we need
to specify the head first.
So linkage list the head and we are searching for that number.
The index number two.
What is the value stored inside?
So here we go.
The first dot for the second one, the third Note five and the fourth note is equal to three.
If we scroll down, this is the iterative way that we have sold in the previous exercise and this is
our exercise number 51.
This is the method that is getting the ends, not data using recursion.
It's very important guys to understand that relation and how to work with linkage list, how to insert,
delete and then search and get and both weight in both ways, the recursion and the third octave.
You may encounter all the questions and recursion, or maybe you encounter the questions and eternities.
OK.
So please practice these exercises.
Please write them down.
These are the methods that we have solved using the or the previous exercises related to Link Atlas.
These are very important exercises and you will advance.
You do, then you level and they and master the data structure and then correct.